Finding Aid for the Getty Research Institute Scholars Program Images and Recordings, 1985-2013 IA20026
Institutional Records and Archives
- Audio recordings, 1987-2001; Series I.; 21.7 Linear Feet (27 boxes); 1741.37 GB (944 files)
  - Scholar Year 1994-1995, Series I.I.; 358.61 GB (205 files)
    - Lectures and presentations, Series I.I.4.
      - Crawford, Margaret. "The Architecture of Everyday Life," Work in Progress Lecture, February 17, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Crawford, Margaret. Part 1, 0590a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Discussion. Part 2, 0590b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0591 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Bolzoni, Lina. "Memory and Invention between the Fourteenth and Sixteenth Centuries," Director's Lecture Series, March 2, 1995; 0592; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Bolzoni, Lina. "The Images of the Printed Page and the Images of the Art of Memory: Two Examples from the Sixteenth Century," Director's Research Seminar, March 9, 1995; 0593; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Marshall, Robert, Jennifer Watts, Victoria Steele, Frances Terpak and Mike Davis. "Collections and Archival Repositories: In Search of Urban History," Panel Discussion, March 13, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0594a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0594b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 3, 0595 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Kort, Pamela. "Beuys, Immendorff and the Arena of the Impassioned Self,", March 14, 1995; 0596; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        Content only contains 4 minutes.
      - Walker, Dean. "Playing with Time: Recent Research on Fiske Kimball's Installation of Period Rooms (1500-1800) at the Philadelphia Museum of Art," Director's Lecture Series, March 16, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0597a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0597b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Siegfried, Susan. "Eroticized Viewing: Women and Boys in Post-Revolutionary French Genre Painting," Work in Progress Lecture, March 17, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Siegfried, Susan. Part 1, 0598a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Siegfried, Susan. Part 2, 0598b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Discussion. Part 3, 0599a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Discussion. Part 4, 0599b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Franko, Mark. "The King's Material Body,", March 21, 1995; 0600; (1 audiocassette and 1 copy) (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Assmann, Aleida. "Stabilizers of Memory: Affect, Symbol, Trauma,", March 23, 1995
        - Original recordings, 0601-0602; (2 audiocassettes)
          - Assmann, Aleida. Part 1, 0601 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
          - Discussion. Part 2, 0602 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Duplication masters, 0951-0952; (2 audiocassettes)
          - Assmann, Aleida. Part 1, 0951 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
          - Discussion. Part 2, 0952 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Use copy, (1 CD) (Enclosure 1996.IA.02-36)
      - Roth, Michael. "Trauma, Representation and Historical Consciousness,", April 4, 1995; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
        Audio files 0608-0609 are copies of 0606-0607
        - Part 1, 0606 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0607 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Settis, Salvatore. "More a Library than a Man," Director's Research Seminar, April 11, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0610 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0611 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Franko, Mark. "Novantiqua: The Choreography of Memory,", April 25, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0617a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0617b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 3, 0618 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Silverman, Debora. "Weaving Paintings: Religious and Social Origins of Van Gogh's Craft Labor," Work in Progress Lecture, April 28, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0622a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0622b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 3, 0623 (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Jacob, Christian. "From the Sphere to the Map: Conceptual Background, Social and Intellectual Practices Around Geographical Maps in the Hellenistic and Graeco-Roman World,", May 2, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0624a (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
        - Part 2, 0624b (Box 1996.IA.02-16)
      - Carruthers, Mary. "'Remembering Heaven and Hell': Invention and Memory in Medieval Monastic Culture,", May 9, 1995; (1 audiocassette)
        - Part 1, 0630a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2, 0630b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Morton, Pat. "Hybridity: Theorizing the Margins of Architecture," Work in Progress Lecture, May 12, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0633 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2, 0634 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Rubin, Gayle, Brian Freeman, Richard Myer, Michael Warner, and Carol Vance. Censorship and Silencing: Practices of Cultural Regulation, May 12, 1995; (4 audiocassettes)
        Part of Richard Myer's lecture is missing. Brian Freeman's lecture is missing.
        - Rubin, Gayle. Part 1, 0635a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Rubin, Gayle. Part 2, 0635b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Myer, Richard. Part 3, 0636a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Warner, Michael. Part 4, 0636b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Vance, Carol. Part 5, 0637 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Discussion. Part 6, 0638 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - L.A. Archives and Collections Series. "The Production of the Authentic Voice: Artists and Scholars as Users of Collections and Archives,", May 15, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0639a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2, 0639b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 3, 0640a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 4, 0640b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Severi, Carlo. "Lasting Words, Lost Writings,", May 30, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0645a (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 2, 0645b (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
        - Part 3, 0646 (Box 1996.IA.02-17)
      - Severi, Carlo. Seminar, June 13, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0649a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 2, 0649b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 3, 0650 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Assmann, Jan. "Moses and the Reinvention of Egypt: Egypt and the Abolition of the Mosaic Distinction,", June 15, 1995; 657-658
        - Original recordings, (2 audiocassettes)
          - Part 1, 0657 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
          - Part 2, 0658 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Use copy, (1 CD) (Enclosure 1996.IA.02-36)
      - Suspects: Culture, Welfare, Community, Defining civic responsibilities in a time of social denial, June 21, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0664a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 2, 0664b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 3, 0645 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Reese, Tom and unidentified artist. Center for the Study of Political Graphics. Lecture., June 28, 1995; 0666; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - L.A. Archives and Collections Discussion Series: Apodaca, Paul, Mayme Clayton, Carolyn Kozo Cole, Kevin Mulroy. "Personal Preference, Collection Policy, and the Historical Record: Public and Private Collectors," Panel Discussion., July 25, 1995; (2 audiocassettes)
        - Part 1, 0667a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 2, 0667b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 3, 0668a (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Part 4, 0668b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
  - Scholar Year 1995-1996, Series I.J.; 199.3 GB (113 files)
    Materials comprise recordings of events, lectures, and discussions held at the Getty during the scholar year 1995/1996. During this time Getty scholars explored the theme "The Nature and Idea of Collecting" as a topic broadly defined to include: the social and institutional practice of collecting; how it reflects the values of a given community, region, and era; systems of display and classification; and the emergence of new languages and classes of collecting. Among the areas studied by this year's Getty Scholars were the collecting practices of Renaissance Italy, the dispersal of the art collections of Great Britain after the Civil Wars of 1640, and the social function of collecting in Oceanic cultures.
    - Mapping Contemporary Native American Culture, March 5-9, 1996; Series I.J.1.; (8 audiocassettes)
      Artists, writers, curators, scholars, and activists from the United States and Canada explored contemporary Native American cultural issues during a week-long series of programs presented by the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities. Through discussion and performance, the participants exchanged ideas, strategies, stories, and histories that mapped the changing cultural topographies of indigenous North America.
      - Champagne, Duane, Suzan Shown Harjo, Edgar Heap of Birds, Robert Allen Warrior. "Indigenous Thought and Intellectual Work,", March 5, 1996
        - Part 1, 0709
        - Part 2, 0710
      - McMaster, Gerald, Jolene Rickard, Greg Sarris and Paul Chaat Smith. "Making Art, Making Indians: Cultural Practices and Native Identities,", March 6, 1996 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Part 1, 0711a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Part 2, 0711b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Part 3, 0712 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Alvitre, Cindi, Lynn Gamble, Lin A-Lul'koy Lotah. "(Re)collections,", March 9, 1996; 713-714 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        Files have no sound.
      - Apodaca, Janine Bowechop, Carey Caldwell, Tom Hill and Duane King. "Museums and Native American Material Culture,", March 9, 1996; 715-716 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
    - Dosso Dossi and His Age, May 9-11, 1996; Series I.J.2.; (13 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
      Materials comprise audio recordings of a series of lectures organized by the Getty Research Institute to examine Dosso's style, artistic influences, iconography, and historical context. The lectures anticipated the Getty Museum's 1999 exhibition, "Dosso Dossi, Court Painter in Renaissance Ferrara."
      - "Mantua in the Age of Isabella D'Este" and "Ferrara in the Age of Alfonso I,", May 9, 1996
        - Part 1, 0954 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 2, 0955 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 3, 0956 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 4, 0957 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 5, 0958 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - "Rome as a Crossroads" and "Style and Iconography,", May 10, 1996
        - Part 1, 0960a (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 2, 0960b (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 3, 0961a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 4, 0961b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 5, 0962a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 6, 0962b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 7, 0963 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Roundtable Discussion, May 11, 1996
        - Part 1, 0743 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 2, 0744 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
    - Bredekamp, Horst. "The Brandenburg-Prussian Kunstkammer,", June 20-21, 1996; Series I.J.3.; (4 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies)
      Materials comprise audio recordings of a series of lectures inspired by the idea of the Kunstkammer, that focus on private collections in the 17th and 18th centuries and the evolution of public museums, particularly in Germany. The lectures were part of the Getty Scholar Program for 1995-1996 that explored the theme "The Nature and Idea of Collecting."
      - Session 1:, June 20, 1996 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Avenarius, Gundula. "The Beginnings of Collecting: The Kunstkammer from the Time of Elector Joachim II to Elector George William, 1535-1640.", 0981a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Matyssek, Angela. "The Kunstkammer Inventory of 1605.", 0981b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Klotz, Katharina and discussion. "The Brandenburg-Prussian Kunstkammer during the Reign of Frederick III/I in Prussia, 1688-1713.", 0982a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Session 2:, June 21, 1996 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Segelken, Barbara. "The Kunstkammer During the Reign of Frederick William I, 1713-1740.", 0985a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Dietze, Peter. "Collecting Activities and Structural Changes from the Late Eighteenth Century.", 0985b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Kornmeier, Uta. "The Dissolution of the Kunstkammer in the Nineteenth Century and the Rise of the Berlin Museum.", 0986a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Discussion., 0986b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
    - Lectures and presentations, Series I.J.4.
      - Rudolph, Conrad. "Hugh of St. Victor's: The Mystic Ark and the Multiplication and Systematization of Imagery in the Early Twelfth Century," Work in Progress Lecture, September 15, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Introduction, 0669a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Rudolph, Conrad. "Huge of St. Victor's: The Mystic Ark and the Multiplication and Systematization of Imagery in the Early Twelfth Century", 0669a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Beyer, Andreas. "Invisible object on idea and concepts in visual art" (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Lecture Introduction, 0670a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Beyer, Andreas. "Invisible object on idea and concepts in visual art"., 0670a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Audience questions and answers., 0670b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Roth, Michael. "The Past that Wounds,", September 15, 1995; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Introduction, 0953a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Roth, Michael. "The Past that Wounds" lecture, 0953a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Discussion, 0953b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Tchen, John Kuo Wei. "Three Enigmatic Pieces from the Wong Whing Foo Virtual Museum,", September 20, 1995; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Introduction., 0671a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Tchen, John Kuo Wei. "Three Enigmatic Pieces from the Wong Whing Foo Virtual Museum", 0671a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Discussion., 0671b (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Bedoya, Roberto. Keynote Conversation. Artists' Organizations. The 10th Annual National NAAO Conference, San Francisco, October 11, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Introduction. Holly Block, 0672a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Keynote Conversation. Artists' Organizations. Guest Speaker, Bedoya., 0672a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Keynote Conversation. Artists' Organizations. Guest Speaker, James Skillen., 0672b1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Keynote Conversation. Artists' Organizations. Guest Speaker, Beracca Sayvey., 0672b2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Discussion., 0672b3 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Session Discussion continued., 0673b1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Joselit, David. "Media as Landscape," Works in Progress Lecture, October 13, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Joselit, David. Lecture on "Media as landscape.", 0674a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Panel Discussion. "Media as Landscape", 0674a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
        - Panel Discussion continued. "Media as Landscape", 0675 (Box 1996.IA.02-18)
      - Eibl-Eibesfeldt, Irenaus. "Biological Aspects of Art and Aesthetics," Director's Lecture Series, October 17, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Introduction, 0676a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Eibl-Eibesfeldt, Irenaus. "Biological Aspects of Arts and Aesthetics." Director's Lecture Series, part 1, 0676b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Eibl-Eibesfeldt, Irenaus. "Biological Aspects of Arts and Aesthetics." Director's Lecture Series, part 2, 0677a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Session Discussion., 0677b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Sutterlin, Christa. "The Message of the Frightful. On Aesthetic Communication in Evil-Warding Figures: An Ethological Approach," Director's Lecture Series, (3 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Session Introduction., 0680a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Sutterlin, Christa. "The Message of the Frightful. On Aesthetic Communication in Evil-Warding Figures: An Ethological Approach," Director's Lecture Series, part 1, 0680b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Sutterlin, Christa. "The Message of the Frightful. On Aesthetic Communication in Evil-Warding Figures: An Ethological Approach," Director's Lecture Series, part 2, 0679a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Session Discussion., 0679b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Bright, Betty. "The Best of Book Arts: A Decade's Perspective,", November 14, 1995; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Introduction on "The Best of Book Arts: A Decade's Perspective", 0683a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Bright, Betty. "The Best of Book Arts: A Decade's Perspective", 0683a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Lecture Discussion, 0683b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Schmitz, Lisa. Artist's presentation, December 4, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Lecture Introduction on "Artist's presentation," Lisa Schmitz., 0687a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Schmitz, Lisa. Artist's Presentation, 0687b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Anderle, Donald, Neville Agnew and Manuel Calisto. "Quito: Preserving a Historic City,", December 7, 1995; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        Please note that the records are incomplete: digital file of recording ends in the middle of Neville Agnew's lecture. Donald Anderle and the session discussion are not contained in the digital file.
        - Session Introduction., 0978a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Manuel Calisto. "Quito: Preserving a Historic City,", 0978a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Neville Agnew. "Quito: Preserving a Historic City." (Incomplete), 0978b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Naef, Weston. Lecture on the creation of photography collection at the Getty museum, December 8, 1995; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Naef, Weston. Introduction., 0688a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Naef, Weston. "Lecture on the Getty museum's photography collection." part 1, 0688a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Naef, Weston. "Lecture on the Getty museum's photography collection." part 2, 0689a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Lecture Discussion., 0689b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Liebmann, Irina. "Nichts war gemutlicher als diese Diktatur — die DDR und ihr Folgen fur dem Geist,", December 12, 1995; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Hyman, Herbert. Session introduction, 0690a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Liebmann, Irina. Lecture on "Nichts war gemutlicher als diese Diktatur- die DDR und ihr Folgen fur dem Geist.", 0690a2 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Session discussion., 0690b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Jones, Amelia. "Vito Acconci's Body Politic: Performing the Subject in Post-modernism," Work in Progress lecture, January 19, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Lecture Introduction. Nancy Troy, 0696a1 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Jones, Amelia. "Vito Acconci's Body Politic: Performing the Subject in Post-modernism," Work in Progress lecture, 0696b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Lecture Discussion., 0697 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Settis, Salvatore. Lecture, January 30, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Settis, Salvatore. part 1, 0698a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Settis, Salvatore. part 2, 0698b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Discussion. part 3, 0699 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Bohn-Spector, Claudia. "Stieglitz's Magisterial Gaze: Photographic New York from Above," Work in Progress Lecture, February 2, 1996; 0700; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Mattusch, Carol. "Seeing Ghosts: In Search of the Greek Bronze Original," Director's Lecture Series, February 8, 1996; (1 audiocassette)
        - Original recording, (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
          - Mattusch, Carol. part 1, 0701a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
          - Mattusch, Carol. part 2, 0701b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Use copy, (2 CDs) (Enclosure 1996.IA.02-36)
      - Reed, Marcia. "The Collector's Books: William Hamilton's Color-Plate Editions," Work in Progress Lecture, February 16, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Reed, Marcia. part 1, 0702 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Reed, Marcia. part 2, 0703 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Pierantoni, Ruggero. "Architecture, Power and Light: The Case of the Pantheon," Director's Seminar, February 29, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Pierantoni, Ruggero. part 1, 0706 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Pierantoni, Ruggero. part 2, 0707 (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Hachivi Edgar Heap of Birds. Artist's Presentation, March 5, 1996; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Part 1, 0708a (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
        - Part 2, 0708b (Box 1996.IA.02-19)
      - Barker, Nicolas. "Hortus Eystettensis: The Garden and the Book, Collecting Plants and Pictures of Plants in Seventeenth-Century Germany,", March 11, 1996; 0717; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Zeitler, Nancy. Works in Progress Lecture, March 15, 1996; 0719; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Mehard, Elizabeth Teresa. "Ancient Eurasian Textiles: New Evidence from the Tarim Basin,", March 24, 1996; 0720; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        First part of lecture not found.
      - Franklin, David. "Polidoro da Caravaggio and his Place in Mannerism," Director's Lecture Series, March 28, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Franklin, David. part 1, 0721 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 2, 0722 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Pucci, Giuseppe. "Screening the Past: Classical Antiquity in Motion Pictures,", April 2, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Pucci, Giuseppe. part 1, 0723a (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 2, 0723b (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 3, 0724 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Cuevas-Wolf, Christine. "Revolution and Photography in Mexico, 1910-1939," Work in Progress Lecture and Discussion, April 12, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Cuevas-Wolf, Christine. part 1, 0725a (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 2, 0725b (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 3, 0726 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Takashina, Shuji. "Presence and Shadow: Aesthetic Sensibility in Japan and the West," Director's Lecture Series, April 18, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Takashina, Shuji. part 1, 0727 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 2, 0728a (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Discussion. part 3, 0728b (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Settis, Salvatore. Press Conference, April 19, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 1 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
        - Part 2 (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Nooteboom, Cees. Reading, April 30, 1996; 0731; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-20)
      - Florescano, Enrique. "Indian Spanish and Liberal Iconographic Traditions in Mexico,", May 14, 1996; 0746; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Goldsworthy, Andy. Artist's presentation, May 15, 1996; 0748; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Phillips, Ruth. "Nuns, Ladies and the Queen of the Huron,", May 15, 1996; 0750; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Lanata, Giuliana. "I am the Sophia of the Greeks, I am the Gnosis of the Barbarians," Director's Lecture Series, May 16, 1996; 751; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Schneider, Lambert. "Classicism in the United States,", June 4, 1996; (1 audiocassette) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 1, 0754a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 2, 0754b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Grigsby, J. Eugene III, Thomas Benitez, Elise Bernstein, Maria Herrera, Joe Hicks, and Dan Miller. "Creating Responsibility: The Intersection of Art and Civic Life,", June 18, 1996; (2 audiocassettes and 1 set of copies) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 1, 0755 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 2, 0756 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
      - Hendrix, Lee. Lecture, June 27, 1996; (2 audiocassettes) (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 1, 0761a (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 2, 0761b (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
        - Part 3, 0762 (Box 1996.IA.02-21)
  - Scholar Year 1996-1997, Series I.K.; 175.08 GB (87 files)